

Viktor Yakovenko

Unity Developer

September 20, 2002

+38 067 872 18 78

viktor.yakovenko.228@gmail.com

Kharkiv, Ukraine

Skills

- Strong knowledge of C#
- Understanding of algorithms and data structures
- Unity
- Git
- · Zenject, Dotween, Unity Assets
- · OOP, SOLID, GoF

Languages

English - Intermediate

Ukrainian – Native

Hobbies & Interest

- Videogames
- Gym
- · Manga & anime
- Mathematics

Links





GitHub



<u>Telegram</u>



Itch.io



Discord

About

I am 21 years old student at Kharkiv National University of Radioelectronics. My first experience of Game Development was in 2017 in GameMaker: Studio. Since 2021, I am interested in game development with a focus on Unity technology. I am the type of person who seizes every opportunity to learn something new. That is why I enjoy challenges. From there, I'm under pressure to learn quickly and gain a lot of new experience.

Experience

Architecture Training (pet project)

Unity developer | November 2023 - Now

This project's aim is to develop a set of approaches and practices that will work for projects of any size. Project provides implementation of DI container for managing Services kind of like Zenject. NavMesh is using for AI Navigation of Enemies. Game starts from Entry Point where creating State Machine which manage the whole game. The method of saving and downloading data about the progress and state of the player has been organized with JsonUtility. Game Logic is using Component Model which involves creating small components for various game objects. Factory Pattern is using for instantiating game objects.



Space Shooter (pet project)

Unity developer | July 2023 - September 2023

Space Shooter is an endless arcade game where the player controls a spaceship and shoots enemies and meteors to earn points. Project uses New Input System and TextMesh Pro. Experience in creating and using Particle System and developing of adaptive UI. Using pattern Strategy for applying damage for Space Objects. Pattern Singletone was used for managing Audio Player.



Sytoss

Full-stack developer | March 2021 - September 2021

Development of the WEB application for Company Resource management. Using ASP.NET Core for the backend, Angular for the frontend, and Entity Framework to implement CRUD operations for database interaction. Entity Framework Code-First approach was used to design database scheme and work with the database. Repository pattern was implemented for work with database. Unit of Work pattern was implementer for coordinating multiple repositories and managing transactions.

Courses

Complete C# Unity Game Developer 2D

Architecture Unity mobile game

Books

CLR via C#, 4th edition © 2012 Jeffrey Richter

Game Development Patterns with Unity © 2021 David Baron

Education



Kharkiv National University of Radioelectronics

Bachelors in Computer Science | Sept. 2019 - June 2023